Hi , my name is tamara
I was born and raised in new york state in the united states
And right now i'm living in ecuador
Which is in south america
My question is , do i like my role at my current job
Yes , i love my role at my current job
Teaching english online to kids in china
Starting each class with basic conversations like asking students to share something
Good about their week or their day
What's their favorite thing about grandpa or grandma
It helps them transition from thinking in chinese to speaking in english
this job helps me in tailoring activities for young and older students
and introducing diverse themes such as nature and landmarks
To topics on brain activity
And how it's used by scientists to discover new technologies
creating a fun environment while encouraging participation
Keeps the students motivated and enhances their language development
Thus , i love being a part of their journey