How did you two meet
We met in college one night
I went to a vegetball game where he was the star player
so i noticed him
And after that he passed by me on the campus
And there was a thing at the time
You're my sp my secret passion
So he passed by me
And said you're my sp
Ha ha
And want to
He was dancing the way they danced and harlem
So daddy , what kind of dancing was that
The lindy oh the lindy
And i didn't know how to dance that way
Sha goody two shot
What did he say
He says you are goody two shoes ! ha
Well that's what they all call me all my life
Tell me about your wedding and how did it happen
She was in a graduated class
it was nineteen forty one
And it occurred to me that i would never see her again
I didn't want to lose this squirrel
I sort of panicked and with nothing to offer her
I asked her to marry me
She to my great delight said yes
I've been lucky
i look upon us as the princes and the pauper
And the prince and the pauper prevail
So far for a three years
And what is the secret to your marriage
I say you have to like the person as well as love
I think lioking is even more important there's really no secret
You just live
You live every day and you become almost one person
So what is your proudest achievement
You ha ha ha
Well i i accept that
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
Is there anything you would like to add
Yeah , i love my wire
ha
i love