It was only about a two minute drive from my house
There was nothing left of that forty unit department building
Except parts of a couple of walls
I left with the clothes on my back because everything was lost
Everything was gone
I was just trying to get myself back on our feet
And then that's when the fire happened
It was like , all right
Well , we're homeless again
You know , i can't do anything about the fire
But the people that were there
That's where my concern was
And most of the people there had family
Their friends that they could go and and stay with
I had nobody
I was scared to death
I said , have to start over again
And i remember being crouched down
And it was you who came up to me
You like it's gonna be okay
What do you need
How can i help you
That day that we spent together was so personal and so emotional
But then we didn't see each other for quite a while
Yeah , it was like five years
And there was another large apartment fire
And the red cross was involved like we always are
I just remember tapping on your shoulder and i'm like charlie it's brittney
I ended up becoming a social worker and the look on your face
You're like no way
Ha ha ha ha ha ha
What a surprise
I know i was so happy to see you again
You do
After that i realized that i
I liked having you in my life
Yes
You're stuck with me
So i'm i'm glad to be there
Isn't a whole lot . we haven't come on
My kids are all older than you
And when you have spare time
You know where you're going to be , right
Yeah
You're gonna be going to fires with me
Yes , i am
You know , you are someone so important to me
And just a friend for life
thank you thank you very much you've changed my life too