The storycorps silver trailer had come down to the tampa bay region
I had to do a little bit of talking to convince her al to be recorded
Ahh , i remember the first time i saw you
You were running a restaurant
i stopped in for breakfast
And it really was love it for a sight
You know , i fall in love with you
Every morning over again . i do
But we've kind of aged difference
Yeah , i just starting to notice that after almost twenty eight years
Yeah , when earl and i found each other
i was twenty five and he was fifty
And age did not mean a thing
But in our interview
I needed to ask a question
Because steve , in my heart
I needed to have the recorded dancer is some
If you should go before me
You gotta give me some wisdom on how to survive without you
I just want you to be happy
Whatever you needed to do to be happy after i'm gone , then do it
If it means getting remarried , fine
If it means not getting married , fine
Whatever makes you happy
But what if i can't be happy without you
You're just gonna have to learn how kiddo
Assuming that i go first
Well , that's true
I plan on being around for armor h
Earl was diagnosed with cancer
And passed away on july ninth of twenty twenty
He was ninety two
I still on occasion will play that whole interview to hear his voice
You know
I'm not really sure what's gonna happen after we die
I know what i hope will happen
What's that i hope that there is an afterlife and that we'll get together again
But if that isn't the case
Then dying is not the most terrible thing
Is just the end of something
It's going to be a tiresome thing to live with for a while
Because you're gonna feel lonely
Don't park yourself in the house in mope
Eventually you will pass
I was lucky enough after i had him for forty two years in my life
I was blessed
I still our legacy together
As an example of how you can have that kind of love
Just endless love
Let's end on a happy note
I love you i love you too