I was in afghanistan in a particularly dangerous combat zone
And she started noticing that there was a lump in her breast
She received the breast cancer diagnosis on november eighteenth , two thousand and five
And so i got to come home
Closing out one battle to start the next
And we did the chemotherapy
We did the radiation
Come may we got the amazing news
They could find not a single trace of the cancer anywhere
And we never really had a honeymoon
So we planned a trip of a lifetime
but then she tells me she can't fill her left leg
And the doctor shares with us
The cancer is back
And i'll never ever forget the doctor looking at us
And says you should go enjoy your trip
Afterwards a few days provoke christmas
We went out so the kids could go see santa claus
And here's this person absolutely racked with all the horrible ess of cancer
But we pack up the oxygen tanks
We pack up the wheelchair
And we go off to the local mall
When else looks at my wife says
You want to talk to santa
A little sparkle in her eye
That conversation was gone ten fifteen minutes
And to this day i have no idea what that conversation was
But i have a picture from that day
Where she's so alive and full of joy and excitement
And so i will tell anyone in the world
Science clause is absolutely real
One day we were talking
And she said , you've got to hartfort
All i have to do is die
You have to keep on living
And she did die near eve two thousand and six
She is right
Living is the incredibly difficult part
And i know that i should be angry at what was taken
But i also recognize what was given
her smile her giving love
and is this sheer magic of it all