when i was a child
television soap operas had organ music
So when most young children would want to be outside playing
I'm watching the soul properous
Not for the storylines
But there was an organ music all day long
I just wanted to play so badly
You facilitated that for me
Cause you was zoned in on music
You were the kind of student that inspires teachers
Well , i appreciate that
I remembered when you came over and told my mother that they should get me an organ
So my father arranged for the organ to be delivered
That was the greatest day of my life
I was very proud of you
But i was so glad that you didn't stop practicing at school
Well , um
That was because the time i would spend with you after school was a respite
My father was abusive physically and emotionally
One day i was so angry
And i remember with every lick
I stared him in his eye
So the time i would spend with you meant less time
I had to be at home
Did you know that i didn't know the specifics
But i knew that you were troubled about something
And playing the organ gave you the peace of mind that you needed at that time
And you will have my everlasting gratitude for that
You know , there were these flashes of kind things from my father
Which always confused the hell out of me
How could you be so damn mean most of the time
But also do things like get that organ
As i got older
i figured it meant
That he was
He was proud of me
Of course he was
He just didn't know how to express it
So we did kind things
And let you know that there's a human being inside that body
Yeah
After studying the organ would you
When i turned thirteen
I was hired by a church
It got me out of my home
And that saved my life
And i thank you
You're welcome
you're my very favorite teacher