My dad always filtered everything down to its simplest form
People thought maybe he wasn't listening
But he would always listen
And then he would form his words very carefully
Words were like his religion
He brought word builders on my mom and dad's honeymoon
My mom complaint
He wanted to just know words
And he loved the sound of words
And how they felt on your tongue
My dad and uncle had a favorite song that they had created , four
Mary poppins called the eyes of love
But while disney said
Could you write something that's more in line with the philosophy of mary poppins
And it was all just falling flat
They were both really depressed
Well , it happened that that day
I was at school
I was about six years old
And , um , they were giving us the oral polio vaccine , uh
You know , it wasn't the shot
So i , you know , stood in line with all my friends
And we all just took this thing
And then i got home
And my dad looked depressed
And all the shades were closed
It was very dark in the house
And i said , oh
We had the , uh , polio vaccine at school today
And he looked at me
He goes , you let someone give you a shot at school did it hurt
And i said , no , no , no
They , they took out this little cup
And put a sugar cube in it
And then dropped the medicine
And you just date it
and my dad looked at me and started shaking his head
And he went over to the phone
And he called dick and told him he had something
And the next day they wrote a spoonful of sugar helps the medicine go down
They have this little recording studio
My uncle usually would play and sometimes my dad would sing back up
Um , and so they would bring home the songs
And i would hear all these songs before anybody else
And he played the spoonful of sugar
And he said , thank you for that song
I think that the love of his family
And each of us kids inspired different things all the time for him
It was kind of like that was his yarn
And he could make it into the most beautiful afghan
he could take the something mundane like that
And see the the magic in it