由SubEasy转录。升级到专业版以删除此消息
Hi, I'm Özlem. I'm from Turkey and here is my question
What are some tips in language learning?
I have been an ESL teacher for over 20 years and I would like to say a few things about language learning
I always see people trying to find a shortcut in language learning
Yes, you can have a shortcut in the sense of time, but I don't believe you can have a shortcut in the sense of effort
So, number one, you should find the reason why do you want to learn this language
For example, if you want to speak fluently, you should focus on speaking and listening activities
I generally see people complaining about the amount of time they have spent and have no result at the end
But when we look closer at their studies, we see that they have not spent enough time in that specific skill they want
And secondly, you should follow a system
If you follow a system, if you have a system, and thirdly, if you have fun, this is very important, you will definitely learn the language
So, have a system and have fun. Love what you are doing. Thank you. See you later. Bye